Valley TV.
Foreign
speech. Foreign speech. Foreign speech.
Credential life insurance
consultant life insurance. Mhm.
If you fail to plan, you are planning to
fail.
policy
paparum.
minimum
maximum 100,000 20,000,000 Ghana cities
that mean00
Okay.
100%
in-laws
extended family member
50% of the cover. Okay.
Okay.
100,000 Ghana cities,000
Ghana
50% cover. Okay.
Okay. qualify 6 months.
Extended family member parent-in-law,
stepparent, foster parents.
Okay.
insurance.
18 years.
Okay.
sign this policy
59 years
and above
30 years
up to 74 years. Okay.
That's right.
Okay. From age 18 to 59. Okay.
Family
up to 74 years. Yes.
here for 3 years.
Cash back of 15%
15%
100,000
years
back
50% of your contribution
insurance.
Okay.
1% of the sum of the main life,000
Ghana
50,000 but 100,000 1%
50,000
>> that's right plus 50,000 50,000 okay
apart from that also
Ghana.
Okay.
All these benefits are there for you.
Your policies basics. Basics.
at a certain stage in life
to a certain level.
11,000
years
in the next 15 years. How much are we
going to pay?
Minimum 100 CDs
maximum 10,000 CDs
every month.
Every month. Okay.
Every 3 months.
Yes. Okay. Minimum one month.
30% 5 10 15 20 25 30%ucation
policy. Okay. Additionally policy
policy education policy
ultimate premier support plan. Okay.
after years
up to 50% of your contribution. 50%.
Yes. And good thing about this policy
will invest it
90%
of investment returns. What it means
Oh, okay.
That's right.
One good thing
because
minimum of 10 years up to a maximum of
25 years
finanic
depending of the age of your
Okay.
Determine
that primary school
20 Yes.
Okay.
Good.
Life planic.
Okay.
death and permanent disability.
Death, total permanent disability and
critical illness.
Yeah.
Stroke
cancer.
This type of cancers, breast cancer,
cancer of the blood, any other forms of
cancers
because
And one good thing about this policy
minimum 100,000 Ghana cities
200,000 300 500,000 or more decided
one year
Every
checkriving
by 5 10 15 25 30%.
10%. Okay.
illness.
How many years?
Okay.
6 months.
After 6 months
permanent disability
100%
illness 50%. Okay.
200.
Okay.
life.
Very good question.
Okay. Most of the time
most of the time
before
Okay.
That means the nest of
Yeah.
Mr.
funeral policy,
investment policy,
any other policies
policy announce
Life insurance
Life insurance policy
number.